# David Conner

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino.

> Status: Fullstack JS Engineer, M.Sc. Digital Media,

Consultant

> Fields: Project Management, Software Development,

Consulting

### **>>>** Education

Virginia Western Community College

2021 - 2023; 2006 - 2008 Mechatronics Systems E.T.

- Studied Computer Science. Dropped out to compete in jamskating at a national level
- Developed and evaluated an algorithm for semi automated scoring of spreadsheet data

Virginia Tech

2004 - 2006; 2008 Computer Science

- Co-Invented a touch table application for medical support, co-developed software (Java)
- Formed a scrum team, mainted project dev server (Debian), surveyed target audience

## **>>>** Education

University of Bremen

2012 - 2015

Master Studies Digital Media

- Studied Computer Science. Dropped out to compete in jamskating at a national level
- Professionalized in research methods, software development and e-assessment

University of Melbourne

2009 - 2010 Semester Abroad

- Mastered six months of study and trans-cultural experience in Melbourne, Australia
- Finished machine programming, information visualization, professional essay writing

University of Bremen

2007 - 2012 Bachelor Studies Digital Media

- ▶ Fundamentals in Computer Science
- ▶ Fundamentals in Computer Science
- Bachelor thesis focused on experimental redesign of the keyboard to support functional illiterates.

### **Summary**

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino.

Currently I develop and evaluate the next generation learning management system with Meteor based on an extensive nursing curriculum for healthcare education. I also love fitness, martial arts, videogames, news and Sci-Fi series.

**Tech:** Meteor, Javascript, Bootstrap, Mongodb, Git,

Webstorm, Sourcetree, Terminal

**▶ Loves:** Global Game Jam, Sci-Fi series, Stackoverflow,

Fitness and Martial Arts

## **Experience**

Virginia Western Community College

2022 - 2023

**Engineering Student Aide** 

- Maintain Ender-3 Pro and Raise3D printers. Synced Ender-3 configurations for PLA plastics
- Created an Autodesk Fusion CNC config for a Velocity CNC. Collected notes on almost all equipment including support links and digital copies of manuals

RAKE Digital

2018

Cloud Engineer

- Used MS SQL table metadata to quickly learn the accounting database schema for Millennium and ReadyPay
- Designed an application stack with LoopbackJS and Angular 6 to automate payroll tasks in Azure

Voxxel (Startup)

2015 - 2017

Founder

- Voxxel enabled fans to score their impersionations of movie quotes and accents
- ▶ Built a Rails API to back prototypes in iOS, Android and AngularJS (with Web Audio)

Oscil8 (Startup)

2011 - 2015

Founder

- Oscil8 was designed to be the "Github for Music Producers"
- Developed a business model and strategic vision

Left + Right (Contract)

2014

Student Assistant / Programmer

- Developed a web service to extend a Ruby on Rails application with reporting on SQL Views
- Cached report results in MongoDB to enable a dashboard

Jumpcloud

2013

Student Assistant / Programmer

- ▶ Full stack development using a NodeJS API and MongoDB
- Integration tests using Mocha, Selenium and Soda